logomaid.com 2013-01-23

# Post Support Ticket- Logomaid Custom Logos, Premade Logos, and Stationery

Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users. **General**  
You acknowledge and agree that Global Solution Partners may change, amend, alter or replace any part of the privacy policy at any time, and that such changes, amendments, alterations or replacements shall be effective as of the time of posting of the amended privacy policy to the web site. You agree to regularly review this privacy policy for changes, amendments, alterations or replacements. If you do not agree with the changed, amended, altered or replaced privacy policy, do not acquire or license a product or service offered by Global Solution Partners and do not use or access the web site or information, material, products or services provided therein. If at any time you wish to withdraw your consent to the collection, use and disclosure described herein of your personal information by Global Solution Partners, you may do so by contacting Global Solution Partners. **What does this privacy policy cover**  
This privacy policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information collected through a website owned and operated by Global Solution Partners. **Use of personal information**  
Global Solution Partners needs certain personal information if you wish to purchase our products, receive our newsletter, or use certain services we provide at this web site.This information may include your personal contact information or your company contact information. Global Solution Partners will use this information in order to reply your inquiries, provide you with requested products and services or contact you regarding new products and services.By accessing the services of Global Solution Partners and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.Global Solution Partners may disclose your personal information when:

  * • we need to respond to court orders or such other legal process
  * • we need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of Global Solution Partners
  * • we find that your actions on our web site violate terms of use or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services
  * • we sell all our business or if Global Solution Partners is acquired by, or merged with another entity

Global Solution Partners retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes identified above or as required by law.
